Thank you for watching.
Here we go. Here we go.
It's time for the "Halo! This time, we'll be talking with Sakura Oda of Morning Musume。 23's Sakura Oda and
Morning Musume。 23, and Daiko Inoue.
This time, we're going to introduce you to the two of them, so please bear with us until the end.
This is Ako-chan's first time to be an MC for Hallo! Please introduce yourself first.
First of all, please introduce yourself.
Morning Musume。 23 17th term member, I'm Daiko Inoue, a 15-year-old junior high school student from Shizuoka prefecture.
My hobby is packing plum sweets, and I'm good at cheering for others.
What did you say? Special ability.
Cheering.
Cheering?
You mean "Flay Flay"?
Yes, sir.
Cheering? Cheer for me?
Flay flay.
Oh, really?
Yes, sir.
You've done that?
I was a cheerleader in elementary school. That's how I got into cheering.
It's just like I imagined.
It suits you.
You must have been very loud.
Yes, it was.
That's right.
And the plum candy?
Yes.
You love plums.
I love plums. I love it.
Do you collect a lot?
I collect a lot.
I love it so much I made a notebook and turned it in to the school.
It's so deep in my heart.
Morning Musume。 23 Concert Tour Autumn Never Ending Employee Show is now underway.
This is your first full-fledged tour, how do you feel about it so far?
Yes, it's fun, of course, but it's not what I expected.
Of course it's fun, but I knew that it was going to be really strenuous.
It made me realize once again how great the seniors are, and it made me want to work harder.
On November 28, we will be holding the Never Ending Employee Show Special and on November 29, we will be holding the Never Ending Employee Show Sanctuary Mizuki Fukumura Graduation Special at Yokohama Arena.
For Mizuki Fukumura, the leader of the 17th term, this will be her graduation show.
This is the first time for the 17th term since before you joined, right?
Yes, it's the first time, isn't it?
You already knew you'd be graduating before you joined, didn't you?
That's right.
That's unusual, isn't it?
At last.
Yes, and when he told me we were going to perform at Yokohama Arena, I saw his face on the Kohalo stay.
You looked so good, Ako-chan.
I'm embarrassed.
I was so surprised.
I was surprised.
I was really surprised to see you at Yokohama Arena.
Two-bass band...
It's amazing, isn't it?
I'm really happy!
Let's do our best.
I'll do my best.
I'll do my best until Yokohama Arena, so please come! We will do our best to make it to Yokohama Arena, so please come and join us!
Now, please take a look at this video.
Here you go.
Words, Music, Arrangement: Hatsune Miku
Lyrics, music, arrangement by Miku Hatsune
Are you not adventurous enough? Are you timid?
Are you in a rut? Are you clinging to stability?
Are you just going crazy in the wild? Are you stuck in the past?
I'm just trying to be right, and I want to destroy that.
Let's try something new.
I don't believe in the same old equations.
You think it's all about you.
Show me why I can't do it.
We can't change, we can't make the bet that we won't.
I'm done with that.
I'm gonna play the real you.
That's right last bar
I want to destroy your love
Oh, if only it were easy
I want to destroy love
Oh, yeah
Woo
Standard conventional Average incessant fad
From within such a framework I'm open to accomplishment
I don't care what the limits are I'll decide the contradictions for myself
Hope is the spotlight that's dusty inside of you
Let's try something new
Let's change ourselves firstLet's change ourselves first.
No more of those old equations.
They're all threats.
Look, I'm tired of looking for reasons why we can't change.
I'm done looking for reasons why I can't change.
I know who you really are.
Don't you? Come on!
I'm not breaking it down
Rock'n'roll Come on break it down now
I'm a good girl
Tokkoma!
Cosplay
Let's try something new. Let's change ourselves first.
There's no such thing as old-fashioned equations anymore.
It's all pretty much gone.
I'm done looking for reasons why I can't do something. I'm done looking for reasons why I can't change.
I'm done looking for reasons why you can't change.
You know what I'm saying? Then come on!
Ah, I want to destroy it.
If you live by my come-on...
I want to destroy it.
Go!
Ah, I want to break it down
I want to destroy the self I've been so cowardly
I want to destroy it
Ah, I want to break it down
Let's go, let's go, let's go
I want to go to the movies on my next day off I want to go to the movies on my next vacation.
What do you want to put out?
Morning Musume。 23's Sakura Oda and
Yumeshita and Akko will be presenting the "Halo! stay!
From here, we would like to talk a little about each other.
I will ask you some questions.
So let's answer them quickly and without thinking too much.
Let's start with the questions
It's been 5 months since I joined Morning Musume。 Ako-chan, who has been a member of Morning Musume。
How do you feel when you are a member of Morning Musume。 When do you feel like a member of Morning Musume。
When I see the way they act.
Ako-chan loves taking pictures.
What is your best recent photo?
A picture of the sun and the sea taken on the terrace.
My motto is "Moroko kanzoku".
What is your current passion?
To write a blog without skipping a beat.
Ako studied musical theater.
What do you think you can use in your current activities?
Dance variations.
This year marks the 25th anniversary of the Halo! Project is celebrating its 25th anniversary this year!
Which songs have you been exposed to the most?
Morning Musume。 s "Romance My Dear Boy".
Hmmm...
Yes, Romance has always been Romance, hasn't it?
Yes.
Let's see...
Oh, when you look at the way they are
I'm a member of Morning Musume。 Morning Musume。
Yes, that's right. Yes, sir.
I've never done any of the songs on that tour.
I learn the choreography by watching the old choreography videos of our seniors.
I learn the choreography by myself.
And when I see the older members dancing in their lesson clothes
I feel like I'm the only one who can see them.
I get it! I know what you mean!
Yes, yes, yes.
It's like, "I can only see them dancing in their lesson clothes.
I understand.
I can see why so many people wore jerseys like this in those days.
I can feel many things that only 25 years of experience can give me.
And you've made the most of your musical studies.
Yes, I have been performing musicals for quite a long time.
I've been performing in various productions since I was in my senior year, and I've had the opportunity to perform in many different productions.
Yes.
At that time, I played a lot of different roles.
I played more non-human roles, such as fairies.
I also did hip-hop.
I also did some hip-hop and some kind of theme park dance.
Mm-hm-hm-hm.
Jazz dance...
Jazz dance, etc.
I was able to experience so many different genres of dance.
Morning Musume。 Morning Musume。
Sling Sling Paradise, for example.
Yeah.
It's different from the usual choreography.
Yeah, yeah.
I think it's really utilized. I think it's a great use of my time.
Thank you very much.
We'll be waiting for your questions for Mr. Oda after the VTR.
Hello! Ste.
Amazing!
That one lie can be the end of everything.
Morning Musume。23
Sugoi Fiver!
Now on sale!
Wake up call It's time to wake up
It's time to enjoy life
The sun is going to light up
Morning Musume。23
Wake up call
Now on sale!
If you have to say it, human being is just a fool
Morning Musume。23
Featuring Mizuki Fukumura
Never ending shine
Now on sale!
Halo! Ste.
Next, I would like to ask a question to Ms. Oda.
Yes, please!
What is the spicy food you are interested in now?
It's an ingredient, but it's green chili peppers.
Yes.
This September, Oda celebrated her 11th anniversary as a member of Morning Musume。 Sakura Oda celebrated her 11th anniversary as a member of Morning Musume。
What would you like to do in your 12th year? What would you like to do in your 12th year?
I would like to talk more with the younger generation.
What is the best word to describe the current 14-member Morning Musume。
Rock.
Which do you like best: sour, sweet or sour umeboshi?
I like sour and sweet umeboshi.
When is your favorite song from the Halo! Project's past songs, which song would you like to perform with Morning Musume。 Project, which song would you like to perform with Morning Musume。
Morning Musume。 Project, "Psychology of a Maiden" by Morning Musume。
Yes, umeboshi.
Sweet and sour.
Yes, sweet and sour.
I can't get enough of eating umeboshi.
That's right.
Yes, but in moderation. I've loved umeboshi since I was a little girl.
I see.
Yes, really.
I used to have them in a jar at home, and I'd get scolded for eating them.
I used to get scolded for eating them, but they were very sour, and that's why I wanted them to be sour, but not too sour.
But if it's too strong, it makes my face go ooh, so I like dried plums that are not too strong.
But I'm really particular about the red ones.
So you prefer red umeboshi to green?
I see.
What about you, Ako-chan?
I've been trying to get into the green ones lately, but the crunchy ones are a little sweeter.
So you're a super sour person?
No, I like sour.
So you're a salty person.
I like salt.
I see.
I was wondering about something else that you would like to do now that you've been a member for 12 years.Yes, one more thing I was wondering... in my 12th year as a member, what is it that you would like to do?
Yes, I would like to talk with the younger generation... I know I'm considered young by some people, but I still think that I would like to be a member of the younger generation...
I joined Morning Musume。 I was 13 when I joined Morning Musume。
Even if I talk to them with the way I felt when I was 13, with the rules and manners of that time, they have their own new common sense.
And I'm very much in tune with that.
I don't think I'm keeping up with them very well because I think I should go forward with them.
What do today's children feel every day?
I'd like to ask them that.
That's right.
Please subscribe to our channel.
I'm Miyabi Natsuyaki.
I'm Ruri Hiramoto from Tea Horse.
I'll do my best.
Let's do our best!
Well, teacher, what shall we make this time?
Today, I'd like to make Western-style okonomiyaki.
I'd like to make a western style okonomiyaki.
Okonomiyaki.
Do you often eat okonomiyaki, Ruri?
Yes, I do.
I'm from Hiroshima Prefecture.
When I lived in Hiroshima
I ate okonomiyaki about two or three times a month.
I see.
Like this.
I think this is fine.
What shall we start with this time?
Okay, that's it.All right, then.
I'd like to start baking.
Let's start baking.
First of all, heat up the frying pan.
It's going to smoke a little bit.
I don't think it's going to smoke.
When it's very hot, add oil.
Now let's start the dough.
Here we go.
Do you have a particular way of baking?
I'm particular.
Nothing in particular.
What is it, fishmeal?
I don't know.
Always in the family
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
I do.
Here you go.
Yes, sir.
About half.
In the middle.
Go on, go on, go on.
Put it in there in a big gulp.
That's about right.
Easy.
Yeah. - Okay.Yeah. - Yeah.
Looks good.
Yeah.
And here we go.
Between medium and low heat.
And then...
Like this, a little bit in the middle.
It should be a little high.
The oil should be floating a little.
Looks delicious.
And when you think it's browning a little bit...
Shape it like this.
It's like building a wall.
That's right, that's right, that's right.
You see a little bit of something stuck on it?
That's burned cheese.
Leave it as it is.
It's like the wings of a dumpling.
That's right.
Looks delicious.
It's so cute.
It's got cheese and potatoes in it, so it's crispy.
The outside of the potato is crispy.
That's because there's so much oil on the outside.
Looks delicious!
How do you flip these over?
The top has to be on fire.
The heat has to be low here.
Slowly and deliberately let it cook through.
The standard for judging is the side. The criteria for judging is the sides.
The sides get harder and harder as they get more and more cooked.
Like a pancake.
It looks good, doesn't it?
The cheese is still crispy on the bottom.
So you don't want it to lose its shape.
First, take it off the pan.
Go to the other side.
If you move it like this, it's away from the pan.
Now you can flip it over.
This is the scary part.
Go for it.
Good.
Very good.
Here's another point
Here's the Miyamizu point
After you flip it over, you don't press it.
In Hiroshima style, you do.
I don't know if I have a strong image of that.
Everyone tends to press down after mixing.
Not from the top, but from the side.
From here.
Just like before, collect them like this.
You can't push from the top, right?
No, you can't.
Absolutely not.
Who do you get along with best?
Other than the tea ceremony horses...
Apart from the tea ceremony horses...
Who do you talk to the most? People who talk a lot
People who talk a lot
But Yuki Hirayama from Angelem
We were the same age from the audition as trainees.
Heh.
She's a good friend.
We can talk about anything.
I'm going to go talk to her.
The surface has already absorbed the first oil.
Okay, that's fine.
Now, let's go a little bit deeper down here.
I'm going to harden the pan again.
Let's make some sauce.
That's good.
It's a Western-style sauce.
What kind of sauce do you call Hiroshima?
Okami sauce. Otafuku sauce.
I love it. -That's right.
Yes, so today, we put bacon and corn in it.
I put a little bit of ketchup to add a little bit of sourness.
You can make it any way you like.
If you use 1×1 or 1×1, you can use ketchup a lot more.
You use a lot more than you think.
I used a little more on the outside to give it a nice aroma.
It smelled good.
I bought this type of mayonnaise today.
I bought this type of mayonnaise today, the pointy kind.
When you're baking it, it looks like a bar, but it's not cool.
So...
You do it like this.That's how you do it, isn't it?
Do you want to do it at home?
I do it at home.
So you do it at home.
Then I guess it's going well.
I'm pretty sure it's already lit.
Are you okay? Yes, I'm fine.
Now for the main event.
The sauce.
Yes, lots and lots of sauce.
Spread it out with the bottom of your spoon.
Beam it all over.
Beam it up!
You can do this either way.
Oh!
Three minutes to show already!
Oh, it's strong, it's good, it's good, it's good, it's good, it's good.
Perfect, perfect, perfect!
Yes, it's done!
Western-style okonomiyaki is ready.
How do you like it, Ruri?
I thought it turned out really delicious.
And since this was the first time I'd made this pattern.
I was really used to it.
And in a good mood.
I've seen it before.
I was so happy.
I'm sure it turned out well.
Let's eat it now!
Bon appétit! Bon appétit.
Here you go.
Bon appétit.
Is it good?
Yum! Yum!
It's so soft and fluffy and super tender.
The corn is delicious.
It's like the point.
I'm so happy for you, doctor.
I wasn't too thrilled today.
I do it all the time.
I make this all the time, doctor.
How was it? You should try cooking, Lulu.
I used to make okonomiyaki at home.
But like you said, I pushed it too far.
That's why.
And when you mix it...
I learned a lot from you.
I learned a lot.
I'd like to try it myself.
That's wonderful.
But you seemed to enjoy cooking.
I'm happy for you.
Thank you very much.
I'd love to see you on Hello Kitchen again.
Thank you very much, Lulu.
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much. Thank you very much, doctor.
That's all for Hello Kitchen!
Bye bye!
That looked delicious.
Actually, I was on Hello Kitchen for the first time a while ago.
I've always hated bell peppers there.
I was supposed to make stuffed peppers.
I made it and it was delicious.
I'm glad you liked it.
I'd like to watch the video again and make it again.
Do you have any recent dishes you've made?
Yes, I recently made pickled cucumbers.
I made all kinds of cucumber pickles.
Of course, I made ume plum pickles.
I also made Korean-style cucumber pickles with soy sauce and other ingredients.
Why did I make so many kinds of pickles?
First of all, I had a lot of plums at home, so I made them to consume them.
When I went to the store the other day, I found a special Tupperware for cucumber pickles.
I was thrilled!
I was so excited!
I couldn't help but want to use it a little more
I couldn't help but make a lot of them!
Which one was your favorite? Tell me one of your favorite recipes.
Shio koji is the best for me.
It's really good if you marinate it in shio koji stock.
Ako-chan is one of the cooking members of Morning Musume。 I have an image of Ako-chan as a cook among Morning Musume。
I have an image of her as one of Morning Musume's cooks. I think there are opportunities for you to cook in the mornings when you wake up.
If there is something you want to cook, you know?
Yes, I do. Yes.
I heard that Japanese food is good.
I've never cooked Japanese food before, so I'd like to try it.
I'm looking forward to it.
Halostei
Next is the presentation of lyrics that resonate with you.
Are there any lyrics or phrases that fit your current mindset?
Yes, I am Morning Musume。 I'm Morning Musume。ヌs "Life Blues".
I think there is a lyric in Morning Musume's "Life Blues" that says, "Life is somehow manageable because you start from an impossible program.
I think there is a lyric in Morning Musume。 I have been a member of Morning Musume。
I've been in the group for 5 months now, and I've never had such a dense and intense experience.
Each day is very fulfilling, but there are also tough times.
But there are times when I feel like I'm going through a tough time, and when I was on the summer tour with the band, I heard the blues of life...
That's what I was doing.
I've come to think that I can make it through those times.
I'm feeling a little more positive now that I'm able to think that I can make it through these times, so the blues of life really resonated with me.
I see.
I, Sakura Oda, was thinking of the song "You're the sun with a smile".
I was a junior high school student at the time, and the lyrics "adults may feel like they're cheating, but adults want to be you again..." really resonated with me.
I was in junior high school at the time, and Tsunku gave me these lyrics.
I thought that adults are the sneaky ones.
Adults can do a lot of things by themselves and decide where they want to go
I used to think that it's fine because I have no choice but to do as I'm told
Now that I'm an adult
I want to go back
I feel that I have a lot of feelings that I can only love.
I've changed my perspective a little bit and it's like a theme song for my life.
I feel that this song is like a theme song for my life.
Please watch the VTR.
Please watch the VTR.Here you go.
A lyrics presentation that touched my heart.
Yay!
In this corner, we will present the lyrics of the songs that resonate with you from Hello! Project's songs that resonate with you, and talk about the appeal of the song lyrics.
Project songs that resonate with you. Project songs that resonate with me, and I will talk about the appeal of the songs.
So, this week, I, Moe Kamiya, would like to make a presentation.
Yes, I am looking forward to it.
Here it is.
I embrace luck in all things that come and go
bangs, back hair, and a one-way ticket that shines all around.
I know, I don't want to wear black and white coats
This is a part of the rap song "I don't want to put on black and white coats.
Yes, yes.
This is the second rap. You look so happy.
I love it.
It's great.
I like it too.
Yes, this is something.
This corner is a presentation of lyrics that touched my heart, isn't it?
Yes, it is.
I was singing this during the live performance, and I knew the lyrics, but I didn't know them at the time,
I was singing this during a live concert, and I knew my part of the song, but I had a chance to sing two lines here, because Ise pin was taking a rest during the concert.
I was so emotional, and I was so happy for what was coming and what was going to come.
I think this is the lyrics of Angulum.
And, although there is a turnover in the lyrics, they are evaluated according to the time period, which is difficult to say.
Well, it's hard to say.
Well, to put it bluntly, yes.
But still, I have been active for many years, and I have had many conflicts, but I still love every era of Angstrom.
But I love every era of Angeleum, so I think that the history of Angeleum has a great history, too,So I wonder what that history is... There is also a great history,
But I also sing with the thought that the current Angelem is the best.
I don't know.
When we had that concert, it was like Calm was singing these two lines and I was singing these two lines.
Yes.
And maybe because these lyrics are linked to my own, Calm sang them in a very emotional and passionate way, and since he lifted them up here like a ritual, it was very easy for me to put my feelings into them.
I was like, "Oh, yeah.
It was like that.
I see.
Yes, I see.
When I look at the lyrics alone, I think it's a little bit different from how I feel about it, a little bit aggressive, like I'm going to go on and on and on. I'm very happy.
I see.
Yes, I see.
The songs that we sing in Ange and the songs of Ange have a lot of links with each other.
Yes.
If they were not linked, I could sing them without thinking about it, but as an expression.
When I hear the echoes of this song, I feel like crying.
Yes, I do.
By the way, how do you feel about it?
Well, I can't see anything coming or going, and I feel heavy about this.
It's okay, it's okay.
I feel like I'm, how should I say it, I'm living my life, you know?
I don't know how to say it.
I haven't lived at all yet, but, you know, in the course of my life, I met a lot of people, and in the midst of them, I am immersed in memories,
Yes, yes, yes.
I remember, I remember such-and-such a thing, such-and-such a thing, and there are many good things and bad things in it,
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
I'm a little bit annoyed by that,
I'm not sure if I'm getting better at this or not.
I am not saying that this is good or that is bad, but I am accepting all of them as wonderful things, and I am taking it all in.I was not thinking about whether this or that was good or bad, but rather, I was accepting all of them as wonderful things, and I was walking through them all.
I'm not saying "this is good" or "this is bad," but I'm saying that I'm taking it all in.
Yes, yes, yes.
Go forward.
Yes, yes. I don't know if this is the right way to take it, but I took it this way.
It's amazing.
That's great.
I think everyone has a different way of receiving things.
It really is different.
Yes, it is. Before we filmed this Halo! Before we started filming for the "Halo!
Yes, it's true.
People see the lyrics in different ways, but there is no such thing as a mistake.
Yes, that's right.
That's right.
That's why.
Really.
Songs are great, aren't they?
Yes.
I don't want to put a caulk on this black and white, like this.
I don't want to wear a coze.
That's right. I like that a lot.
Yes.
I think it tells people that it's okay not to wear black and white.
That's right.
That's good.
Yes, that's good.
Yes, it's good. I really don't have enough time for this.
Really.
Really. Really.
Yes.
I'm going to get excited about it, but, well, here's what I'm going to do.
End of video. So, please look forward to the next one.
Enjoy.
Morning Musume。 23 with Sakura Oda,
Sakura Oda of Morning Musume'23 and Ako Yumigeta of Halo! STE.
We'd like to get to know you better, so we'd like to dig a little deeper.
I've asked her manager about the episode of "Who is this Ako Yumigita? I would like to introduce some of the episodes that I heard from her manager.
What I think is cute about Akiko Yumigita is that her thoughts immediately come out on her face.
She is very cute and shows her face when she thinks. You can see it in the expression on her face when she announced the performance of "Aline Yokohama" to the members on Halo!
It's like that in everyday life.
That's right. I'm a little embarrassed because I tend to show my feelings of surprise.
It's on my face and in my words.
Do you feel it?
I think, "How honest she is!
Oh, but your face is ripped.
Yes.
You're aware of it?
No, I'm not aware of it,
Oh, really?
I was surprised when I saw it.
Why do you have a face like this?
Now, let me make another announcement.
This one is from me,
This is the daily ding-dong incident between Nimigata Ako-chan and Inoue Haruka-chan.
I often see them talking to each other in contrast to Haruka Inoue.I often see her and Haruka Inoue in contrast anyway, and their conversations are always crossing each other's paths.
I have seen Ako-chan tell Inoue that his questions and replies don't always match.
Really, it's the exact opposite, isn't it?
It's the exact opposite.
I didn't expect it to be so opposite,
Yes, it's the complete opposite.
Even your mind is the complete opposite.
Really.
That's right. Even at that time,
Ako-chan found some sweets that she thought Haruka would like,
I was like, "If I buy this for Haruka-chan, will she eat it? I said something like, "If I buy this for Haruka, will you eat it?
I said, "What was it?
I don't know.
You don't know? You mean you don't know if she wants to eat it? I said, "No, I don't know that candy.
I told him that the question and the answer didn't match.
But it happens often, doesn't it?
Yes.
But it just so happens that they buy the same snacks,
Yes, that's right.
But, you know, they never share the same taste.
But, they never share the same taste, only the same snacks,
It's cute, but I've never seen such a relationship between two people.
Really?
Yeah.
I got the impression that they were too small to be like this.
Oh, wow.
I have the impression that they are qualified.
I often think that if it weren't for Haru, it wouldn't have been possible, and if it weren't for Ako-chan, it wouldn't have been possible.
That's true.
That's true.Yes, that's right.
So, we are not close, but we understand each other more and more, and in a good way, we are like airs and graces to each other.
Yes, that's right.
Like we are all natural at once.
Yes, we are becoming more and more like that, like partners.
I think we are becoming more and more like partners, and I hope everyone will continue to look forward to watching us.
So, Ako-chan, let's greet everyone again.
Yes, I'm Ako-chan.
It's been 5 months since I joined Morning Musume。 It's been 5 months since I joined Morning Musume。 I think it's a time when we get used to it in both good and bad ways, so I'd like to continue to work hard without forgetting the spirit of "Moroko kanke" (perseverance).
This is Ako Migita.
Hello! Sta.
Camellia
LaLaLa...
Haloste
On September 9 and 10, the 25th anniversary concert of the Hana-U Project was held.
Looking back on the two days, what impressed you the most, Ms. Oda?
Yes, I remember the first time I saw off a senior member after joining Morning Musume。 I joined Morning Musume。 and the first person I saw off was Reina Tanaka,
We didn't have much time to work together,
I realized that there were still many things I had not fully learned from her,
I felt again that there were many things I had not yet learned from Tanaka,
I felt that there were many things that I had not yet learned from Mr. Tanaka, and I was able to see him dance and hear the sounds that he made,
He recorded all the sounds that I could not hear,
I thought that I could hear a lot of sounds by watching Mr. Tanaka,
I thought I could hear a lot of sounds when I watched Mr. Tanaka, and I really learned a lot from him,
Even after all these years, I still learn something new every time I meet these wonderful senior staff members,
I am grateful to have such a wonderful environment.
From the Hello Project 25th Anniversary Concert,
This time, we will see the jokes of love with selfishness.
How was your first time performing with Masaki Sato?
During the rehearsal, we, the 17th term, were not in the helpmeet, During the rehearsal, we in the 17th period did not conduct the helpmeet,
rehearsal by being allowed to watch the help-me from the front audience side,
At that time, the current members of the group,
Mr. Sato, too,
Members?
I guess that's how we felt.
I was really impressed,
I really liked Ms. Sato in the live video,
I really liked Morning Musume。 I really felt that way, not as a member, but as a member,
I was able to see Morning Musume,
It was really like the feeling I had when I went to Shizuoka Park for the first time,
It was like the first time I came to see them.
It really made me want to wave a penlight,
I don't know.
I really felt like I wanted to wave a penlight when I first saw Morning Musume。 I don't know,
I don't know, it was so cool,
I was really shaken.
It was great.
I knew Ms. Sato very well, so I was very happy to see her,
I knew her well,
Even though it had been a long time since we had met, nothing had changed,
I was wondering if I had really been working by myself for the past one year,
I was depended on for everything,
You were relied on for everything, even in the dressing room, weren't you?
Yes, I was always next to him in the dressing room,
I was explaining things to him.
You are not going to the daytime show, but I am going to the daytime show now, so I don't have time for that.
It was very interesting.
He said something like, "Now you are not allowed to talk to me.
But still, I was standing next to him the whole time,I mean, he said something like that, but still, all the time, you know, next to me, something like that,
He's an interesting guy, isn't he?
It was interesting, Mr. Sato.
Yes, if you meet him, you can have an episode with him soon.
That's what I think of Masaki Sato.
Please have a look. Please take a look.
Wake up Momma, Ki no Momma, Joke of Love
Joke that only girls can understand
Joke that only a girl can understand
Remember, I'm coming.
Wake up Momma, Ki no Momma, Joke of love
Totally different and lonely Meaning that you can be good at it
Don't say I'm in love with you, I'm such a person
Hey Hey Hey, what's in your heart
From the real me
Don't mind Osaka-fu dakaruka, oceanic
Don't lose, don't lose, don't want to lose
I can't fake it with a smile
I don't need love even if I'm good at it
I'm not afraid of anything
Love is one piece
SWING!
Love is better in the heart
I want to be loved I want to be loved
I want to be loved
I'm not so angry with my friends
I don't think I'm lonely Who's being too loud?
Hey Hey Hey I'm getting pimples
I'm not stressed.I'm not stressed.
Why are you talking about me?
You and that day.
Hey Hey
Sadness. Sadness. Pieces of sadness.
Take it home with you.
I don't know what you're going through
Take it home with you and break it
Love should be one
Love should be more painful
Sadness, soul, a piece of sadness
Take it back with you
I don't care what you're going through
Please don't replace it
Love must be sinful
Love would be better in this body
I want love to be more like me
I can't love you
Love
I'm still
Stupid mama, love's a joke
I'll only say goodbye to the girls
Stupid mama, chi no mama, love jokes.
I love you for trying so hard
Morning Musume。 23 Sakura Oda and
Yumige and Akko present Halo! Sta. Yumige and Ako present Halo! stay!
It's time to say goodbye!
Here is an announcement!
New single
Sukkousoku Fever! Wake Up Call
Wake Up to Never Ending Shine is now on sale!
Sukkoukou Fever and Wake Up Call
are the songs that just stick in your ears and get you in the groove.
and you can get into a groove with them.
The song "Neverending Shine" was written by Mizuki Fukumura, the leader of the group.
is the graduation song of our leader, Mizuki Fukumura.
We are singing this song with the feeling of pushing her back.
Please listen to it!
Morning Musume。23 Concert Tour Autumn
The Neverending Shine show is now underway!
The next show will be held on November 11 at Shimane Park
Hiroshima Park on November 12!
Shimane and Hiroshima will be the first time for me to visit both places in my life.
I am very much looking forward to it.
I will do my best!
On November 28th, we will have the Lever Ending Employee Show Special and on November 29th, we will have the Lever Ending Employee Show Sanctuary, Mizuki Fukumura Graduation Special at Yokohama Arena.
I am very happy that we are going to Yokohama Arena for 2 days, and also to see off our leader's graduation.
I will also cherish and enjoy the precious time with OG seniors on the 28th!
I'm looking forward to seeing you all! Project is a channel where more and more members of Hello! Project members will appear on the channel!
Project members every Wednesday, so please subscribe to our channel!
My companions were Sakura Oda and Taako Yumike from Morning Musume。 23.
Good bye!
Thank you for watching!